curezone.com 2010-05-14

# Privacy Policy Statement,CureZone.com

**Privacy Policy**

CureZone takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

  * CureZone respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use CureZone services. Individually identifiable information about you is never disclosed to any third party!

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * CureZone does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies.

    * Your email address is protected on CureZone and the only people who have the access to your email address are the members of the CureZone team.

    * The members of the CureZone team must have the access to your email address in order to do their job - communicate important messages to you.

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.**

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how CureZone treats personal information that CureZone collects and receives, including information related to your past use of CureZone services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of websites that CureZone does not own or control. In addition, certain CureZone associated websites such as [Google](http://www.google.com/privacy.html), [ Amazon](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/468496/002-3572048-1743221), [PayPal](https://paypal.com/) and [ Altavista](http://www.altavista.com/web/legal/privacy) have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on the links.

**CureZone and Cookies**

  * Upon your first visit to CureZone, CureZone, like many other web sites, sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small text file containing a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user.

  * Cookies can not be used to infect your computer with viruses!  Cookies can not be used to collect information about you that you don't wont to disclose (name, address, phone, email)

  * CureZone uses cookies to improve the quality of our service. CureZone does this by storing user preferences in cookies. CureZone will never disclose its cookies to third parties.

  * Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the CureZone Service may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

**Third Party Cookies on CureZone**

  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on CureZone displaying Google AdSense for content ads. When you visit CureZone and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on your browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help Google better serve and manage the ads on CureZone and across the web.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CureZone.

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on the pages you visited on CureZone and other sites on the Internet.

  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**What Information Does CureZone Server Collect?**

  * CureZone does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

  * CureZone server, just like any other web server, logs and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each page visit. That information is used to trace web site usage and to provide more relevant services to individual users.

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

  * CureZone collects personal information when you register with CureZone, when you use CureZone forums or when you subscribe for CureZone newsletter.

  * When you register we ask for information such asemail address, while all other information is optional: your name, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests.Once you register with CureZone and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

  * CureZone automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, CureZone cookie information, and the page you request.

  * CureZone uses information for the following general purposes: to customize & fulfill your requests for services, to improve our services, to contact you and to conduct research.

**Children**

  * We do not collect any personal information from a child under age 13.

  * We do not allow children under age 13 to join curezone forums.

  * CureZone does not ask a child under age 16 for more personal information  
(name, address, phone,  ...).

**Cookies**

  * CureZone may set and access CureZone cookies on your computer.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

**General**

  * You can edit your CureZone Account Information, including your email address.

  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the CureZone service, such as **service announcements** , **administrative messages** and special issues of the CureZone Newsletter, that are considered part of your CureZone account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

  * You can delete all your personal information inside your CureZone account by visiting this page.  But, you can not delete you username.  Certain information, like you email address might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Children**

  * Parents can review, edit, and delete information relating to their child's CureZone account only with the child's permission.

  * If a parent chooses not to allow us to further collect or use a child's information, parents must contact the webmaster.

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to members of the CureZone team who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide  services to you or in order to do their jobs.

  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

  * To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read Security at CureZone.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * CureZone may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your CureZone account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please contact webmaster.

* * *

Read our disclaimer!

* * *

  * **Home**

    * **Terms& Conditions of Use**

    * **Privacy Policy Statement**

    * **Universal Spam Policy**

    * **Security at CureZone**

    * **Forums **

      *  **Posting Guidelines** ****

      * **About Forums**

      * **Disclaimer**

* * *
